{
    "id": "9b360d9b267942c1acfb1dcc3853999e",
    "title": "Adverbs of Frequency",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "He often comes very ................................. to the class.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "late",
                "lately"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "ce96a70c096347fba3a9f97105cc19af"
        },
        {
            "question": "He came here two months ..................................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "ago",
                "before"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "7d6ae30d98a345f09d55b054d75e5e22"
        },
        {
            "question": "He .................................... to our house.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "often comes",
                "comes often"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "9464ec852b404871928b5d63a6ed2d1d"
        },
        {
            "question": "Though James worked very .............................., he failed.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "hard",
                "hardly"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "d68a806d71a44dac90abd8003c63380e"
        },
        {
            "question": "But Peter, who took things .............................., passed.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "easy",
                "easily"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "c655568f76c348838e468f50f8b30d9a"
        },
        {
            "question": "He .............................. comes to see me.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "seldom",
                "ever"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "f846655749b3480cad14794c9b338dc6"
        },
        {
            "question": "I .................................... to meet him.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "always have wanted",
                "have always wanted",
                "have wanted always"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "87d2e9a0583142a8b285d353d0243e06"
        },
        {
            "question": "He is ................................. lazy fellow.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "rather",
                "a rather",
                "rather a"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "78e92598fd8d4b96827937c7f4e13271"
        },
        {
            "question": "I have never seen such a man he is ............................. noble.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "so",
                "too"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "681cfcb4172147c8896a563fbdd43868"
        },
        {
            "question": "When I met John last summer he told me that he had lost his father two years .....................................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "before",
                "ago"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "42855b4fe61e4bf0ae23a981e513dd15"
        }
    ]
}